

Lasse Lund-Egmose

Contact

☑ lasse@lle.engineer

+45 23 90 21 19

🗰 lle.engineer

in /Lasse-Lund-Egmose

Interests

- Engineering
- Cybersecurity
- **Ethical Hacking**
- Cryptography
- Embedded Systems & IoT
- Operating Systems (kernels)
- Project Planning & Mgmt

Passion for technological engineering

Ever since I at an early age experienced the feeling of creating something that is comprehensible by a computer, I have known that I have a great interest in technology. Since then, I've worked hard to continuously broaden my skill set. I began my career with a focus on development of websites and more involved web solutions, but in the recent years, I have shifted focus after finding a great interest in the complex technological areas of cybersecurity and embedded systems. Currently, I am studying a master's degree in Computer Science & Engineering (specializing in computer security) at Technical University of Denmark. In combination with my bachelor's degree in Software Technology, this will result in a Master of Science in Engineering degree (cand.polyt) in 2024.

Work experience

Teaching Assistant — Technical University of Denmark

Kongens Lyngby, 2022

For the exercise sessions of the course "Introduction to Software Technology", I was hired to support the learning process of the students taking the course during exercise sessions.

Backend Developer — Morningscore

Remote, 2019-2021

Hired to develop parts of the Morningscore application remotely, where I worked on major projects, I had a great amount of responsibility, and I had to meet my deadlines — and did. I primarily dealt with the complex task of integrating towards other systems such as the payment gateway (Stripe) or the CRM system (HubSpot).

Backend Developer / Project Manager — Morning Train

Odense C, 2018-2019

Full-time programming and project management job at a web agency, where I made websites and web solutions tailored to the needs of our customers. I also underwent a sales training program by "SalgsPiloterne".

Education

MSc. in Computer Science & Engineering – Technical University of Denmark Kongens Lyngby, 2022-now I am currently studying a master's degree in Computer Science & Engineering at Technical University of Denmark towards a Master of Science in Engineering degree (cand.polyt) degree. The courses I follow align with the Computer Security study line. I expect to graduate in the summer of 2024.

BSc. in Software Technology – Technical University of Denmark GPA: 11.18 Kongens Lyngby, 2019-2022 I followed a wide variety of courses to learn the central aspect of software engineering. I also studied abroad at University of Leeds in the fall of 2021.

High school - Sct. Knuds Gymnasium GPA: 10.4

Odense M, 2015-2018

I followed the natural sciences study line. Furthermore, I was a member of The Academy for Talented Youth (ATU), and I was hired by Sct. Knuds Gymnasium to work as tutor in my final year.





